Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (14 of 15) [labeled on cassette as Kick-off, Punt Return, PAT/FG Block] (1), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (15 of 15) [labeled on cassette as Kick-off, Punt Return, PAT/FG Block] (2), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Original), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 1 minute, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #1), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Original), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #1), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 109)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #1), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (9 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #1), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (10 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (11 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Original), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (12 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #1), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (13 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-Wide] (1 of 2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-Wide] (2 of 2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight], 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline-Wide] (1 of 2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline-Wide] (2 of 2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight], 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (9 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (10 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Punt, Kick-off Return, PAT/FG] (1), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (11 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Punt, Kick-off Return, PAT/FG Block] (2), 16 Sept. 1989 (Carton 75)
- Red and White Game, 1989 (Carton 65)
- Defense (1 of 14) (Blitz: Rip 1, Rip 5, Fire 5 Read, Fire 1), 1989 (Carton 65)
- Defense (2 of 14) (Blitz: Cover 7 vs. Run, Cover 6 vs. Pass, Cover 6 vs. Run), 1989 (Carton 65)
- Defense (3 of 14) (Blitz: Cover 7 & 8 vs. Pass), 1989 (Carton 65)
- Defense (4 of 14) (Combo Alert 5: Run, Pass), 1989 (Carton 65)
- Defense (5 of 14) (Combo Alert 9: Run, Pass), 1989 (Carton 65)
- Defense (6 of 14) (Cover 1 vs. Pass: Under, Under Eagle, Slide), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Defense (7 of 14) (Cover 1 vs. Pass: Slide-Eagle, Slide-Eagle-G, Slide / Cover 1 vs. Play Action: Under, Under Eagle, Slide, Slide-Eagle-G, Split), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Defense (8 of 14) (Cover 1 vs. Run: Slide, Slide-Eagle-G, Slide Eagle, Split), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Defense (9 of 14) (Cover 1 vs. Run: Under), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Defense (10 of 14) (Cover 1 vs. Run: Under, Under-Eagle, Slide), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Defense (11 of 14) (Cover 5: Split, Under, Double Eagle), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Defense (12 of 14) (Cover 9, Cover 2), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Defense (13 of 14) (Short Yardage/Goaline: Stud, Rhino, Stud Double Eagle), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Defense (14 of 14) (Solid Cover 3, 3 Man, 4), 1989 (Carton 66)
- Pass Defense (game-by-game): Maryland, Georgia Tech, Wake Forest, 1989 (Carton 75)
- Recruiting, 1989 (Carton 75)
- Rushing, 1989 (Carton 75)
- Scrimmage (End Zone copy 1), 17 Aug. 1989 (Carton 67)
- Scrimmage (End Zone copy 2), 17 Aug. 1989 (Carton 67)
- Scrimmage (Sideline) [1 of 2], 17 Aug. 1989 (Carton 67)
- Scrimmage (Sideline) [2 of 2], 17 Aug. 1989 (Carton 67)
- Scrimmage (Tight), 19 Aug. 1989 (Carton 67)
- Scrimmage - Afternoon (Tight, End Zone), 21 Aug. 1989 (Carton 67)
- Junior Varsity Scrimmage (End Zone and Sideline copies), 31 Aug. 1989 (Carton 67)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (1 of 8) [labeled on cassette as 1st half], 6 Oct. 1990 (Carton 75)
  U-Matic S cassette; Approximate runtime: 20 minutes; color; sound
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (2 of 8) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half], 6 Oct. 1990 (Carton 75)
  U-matic S cassette; Approximate runtime: 20 minutes; color; sound
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (3 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Sideline], 6 Oct. 1990 (Carton 75)
  Beta SP cassette; Approximate runtime: 20 minutes; color; sound
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (4 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Sideline 1], 6 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (5 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Sideline 2], 6 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (6 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Sideline 3], 6 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (7 of 8) [labeled on cassette as End Zone 1], 6 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State University (8 of 8) [labeled on cassette as End Zone 2], 6 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 11), 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Offesnse, Sideline-End Zone], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Defesnse, Sideline-End Zone], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1-4], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2-4], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Clemson (8 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3-4], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Clemson (9 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 4-4], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Clemson (10 of 11) [labeled on cassette as End Zone], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Clemson (11 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 19 Oct. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Offense], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Defense], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 11) [labeled on cassette as 1st half], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 11) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Post-game], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Duke (9 of 11) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 1], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Duke (10 of 11) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Duke (11 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 10 Nov. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 9) [labeled on cassette as JP Sports Clean Feed Reel 1 of 3], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 75)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 9) [labeled on cassette as 2 of 3], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (3 of 9) [labeled on cassette as 3 of 3], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (4 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (5 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (6 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (7 of 9) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 1], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (8 of 9) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (9 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 8 Sept. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Offense], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Defense], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Tape 1], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Tape 2], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Tape 3], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 79)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Maryland (9 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Maryland (10 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 4], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Maryland (11 of 12) [labeled on cassette as End Zone], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Maryland (12 of 12) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 22 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. San Diego State University, 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 18) [labeled on cassette as 1], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 18) [labeled on cassette as 2], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 18) [labeled on cassette as 3], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 18) [labeled on cassette as 4], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Kick], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 18) [labeled on cassette as #1], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 18) [labeled on cassette as #2], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Tape 1], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (9 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Tape 2], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (10 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Tape 3], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (11 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Tape 4], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 76)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (12 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (13 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (14 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, Endzone 3], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (15 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, Endzone 4], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (16 of 18) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 1], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (17 of 18) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (18 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 27 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Southern Mississippi (All-American Bowl) [labeled on cassette as Endzone, 2nd half], 28 Dec. 1990 (Carton 91)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Defense], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 11) [labeled on cassette as #1], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 11) [labeled on cassette as #2], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Postgame], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Final Play], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
  VHS cassette; Approximate runtime: unknown; color; sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (9 of 11) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (10 of 11) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 1], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (11 of 11) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 29 Sept. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 7), 13 Oct. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 13 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 13 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3], 13 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 7) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 1], 13 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 7) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 13 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Kicks], 17 Oct. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (1 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Defense] (1), 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (2 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Defense] (2), 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (3 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Defense] (3), 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (4 of 14) [labeled on cassette as 1], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (5 of 14) [labeled on cassette as 2], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (6 of 14) [labeled on cassette as #1], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (7 of 14) [labeled on cassette as #2], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (8 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 80)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (9 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (10 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (11 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 4], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (12 of 14) [labeled on cassette as End Zone], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (13 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, End Zone], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (14 of 14) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 4 Nov. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-End Zone], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline], 15 Nov. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline-End Zone], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 22) [labeled on cassette as #1 TV], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 77)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 22) [labeled on cassette as #2 TV], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Postgame], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (9 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Tape 1], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (10 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Tape 2], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (11 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Tape 3], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (12 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Tape 4], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (13 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Tape 5], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (14 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Reel 1], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (15 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Reel 2], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (16 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Reel 3], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (17 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (18 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (19 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (20 of 22) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 4], 15 Spet. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (21 of 22) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 1], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (22 of 22) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 15 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (1 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Offense], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (2 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (3 of 12) [labeled on cassette as defense, Sideline-End Zone], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (4 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (5 of 12) [labeled on cassette as #1], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (6 of 12) [labeled on cassette as #2], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (7 of 12) [labeled on cassette as WRAL], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 78)
  U-matic S cassette; Approximate runtime: 6 minutes, 50 seconds; color; sound
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (8 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 1], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (9 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 2], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (10 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Sideline, 3], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (11 of 12) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 1], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (12 of 12) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 1 Sept. 1990 (Carton 81)
- Recruiting (on cassette with 1967 Tape, 1988 Highlights), 1990 (Carton 59)
- Inventory of footage on 1967 Tape, 1988 Highlights, 1990 Recruiting, 1967-1990 (Carton 59, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on cassette as NC State vs. Clemson, South Carolina, Virginia Tech post-game interviews], 1990 (Carton 110)
- Spring Scrimmage, 31 Mar. 1990 (Carton 81)
- Mike Cofer Interview in Charlotte at Cofer's House, 17 July 1990 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Offense, 1], 26 Oct. 1991 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Offense, 2], 26 Oct. 1991 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Defense, 1], 26 Oct. 1991 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Defense, 2], 26 Oct. 1991 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 26 Oct. 1991 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 7) [labeled on cassette as 1st half, End Zone], 26 Oct. 1991 (Carton 81)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 7) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half, End Zone], 26 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Tight], 16 Nov. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Wide], 16 Nov. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Tight], 16 Nov. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Wide], 16 Nov. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Defense, 2], 16 Nov. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Kicks], 16 Nov. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 8) [labeled on cassette as 1st half, End Zone], 16 Nov. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 8) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half, End Zone], 16 Nov. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Wide], 15 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Tight], 15 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (3 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Wide], 15 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (4 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Tight], 15 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (5 of 7) [labeled on cassette as Kicks], 15 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (6 of 7) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 1], 15 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (7 of 7) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, 2], 15 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Kent State (1 of 5) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline], 14 Sept. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Kent State (2 of 5) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline], 14 Sept. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Kent State (3 of 5) [labeled on cassette as Kicks, Sideline], 14 Sept. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Kent State (4 of 5) [labeled on cassette as 1st half, End Zone], 14 Sept. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Kent State (5 of 5) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half, End Zone], 14 Sept. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Marshall (1 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-Tight], 19 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Marshall (2 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-Wide (Part 1)], 19 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Marshall (3 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-Wide (Part 2)], 19 Oct. 1991 (Carton 82)
- NC State vs. Marshall (4 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline-Tight], 19 Oct. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Marshall (5 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline-Wide], 19 Oct. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Marshall (6 of 8) [labeled on cassette as Kicking, Sideline], 19 Oct. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Marshall (7 of 8) [labeled on cassette as 1st half, End Zone], 19 Oct. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Marshall (8 of 8) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half, End Zone], 19 Oct. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-Tight], 23 Nov. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-Wide], 23 Nov. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Offense, Sideline-Wide (2)], 23 Nov. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline-Tight], 23 Nov. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline-Wide], 23 Nov. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 9) [labeled on cassette as Kicks, Sideline-Wide], 23 Nov. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 9) [labeled on cassette as 1st half, End Zone], 23 Nov. 1991 (Carton 83)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 9) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half, End Zone], 23 Nov. 1991 (Carton 83)